Deepak Panchariya

Jaipur, Rajasthan, India



panchariyaofficial1@gmail.com





linkedin.com/in/deepak-panchariya-55a20b7b

Summary

An individual with **2+ years** of experience in Android Development. Career goal is to become a fully-qualified and experience software's developer, with long-term aspiration of moving into engineering management. I remain flexible with time and dedicated with on time deliveries. Focus on growth and new learnings.

Experience

Software Engineer

ARKA Software's (Nov 2021 – Present)

- Worked with new technologies like Clean Architecture (MVVM), Hilt, Navigation components, Coroutines, Room DB, Google MLKit, Razor pay, Cashfree.
- Worked on Project like Offline and Online chat application with on-the-go language translation
- Notification capture service for Universal Sound Box.
- Board game like Housie, E-Learning platform that offer offline content and test series with student report card.
- Projects: Housie, MsingiPack, Voizpe, JabyJob, OfflineChat

Associate Android Developer

VolanSoft Technologies Private Limited (Apr 2021 – Nov 2021)

- Single handedly manage and develop online Matka Applications (Number Bidding)
- Owned features like Add, Deposit money using Razor pay
- Social login, Firebase, Crash Analytics
- Projects: <u>Laxmi Matka</u>, <u>Deep Matka</u>

Android Developer

NLET Initiatives (Jan 2018 – Jun 2018)

- First-hand industry experience in android Application development. Developed apps, handling different size screens.
- · Gained knowledge of coding principles, Design and Task Breakdown.
- *Worked on School Management E-Platform Project

Education



Rajasthan Technical University, Kota

Master of Computer Applications - MCA (2019 - 2021)



Poornima University

Bachelor of Computer Application - BCA (2015-2018)

Honors & Awards



Smart India Hackathon Edition 2020

Secure runner-up position with problem statement of "Rain Water Harvesting".



Employee of the month

VolanSoft Technologies Private Limited (Jul 2021)

Skills

Zeplin, Kotlin, Java, Basecamp, Git, Bitbucket, Dependency Injection, Espresso Testing, Unit Testing, App versioning, Debugging